/*jshint esversion: 11 */
const easyquestions = [
  {
    "question": "Which is the highest voice?",
    "choice1": "Bass",
    "choice2": "Alto",
    "choice3": "Soprano",
    "choice4": "Tenor",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {
    "question": "W.A. Mozart was a composer from which period?",
    "choice1": "Baroque",
    "choice2": "Classical",
    "choice3": "Romantic",
    "choice4": "Modern",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {
    "question": "What are the names of the 4 main historical periods in music?",
    "choice1": "Baroque, Classical, Impressionism, Modern",
    "choice2": "Baroque, Classical, Romantic, Impressionism",
    "choice3": "Baroque, Romantic, Modern, Contemporary",
    "choice4": "Baroque, Classical, Romantic, Modern",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {
    "question": "The cello belongs to what family of musical instruments?",
    "choice1": "String",
    "choice2": "Brass",
    "choice3": "Woodwind",
    "choice4": "Percussion",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "How many completed symphonies did Beethoven compose?",
    "choice1": "104",
    "choice2": "5",
    "choice3": "9",
    "choice4": "41",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "What woodwind instrument can play the highest pitch?",
    "choice1": "Clarinet",
    "choice2": "Piccolo",
    "choice3": "Flute",
    "choice4": "Oboe",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "How many keys are there on a standard piano keyboard?",
    "choice1": "64",
    "choice2": "88",
    "choice3": "92",
    "choice4": "104",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {  
    "question": "Vivaldi wrote 4 concertos known as 'The Four Seasons'. What is the featured solo instrument in these concertos?",
    "choice1": "Piano",
    "choice2": "Trumpet",
    "choice3": "Violin",
    "choice4": "Oboe",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these instruments would NOT have been heard in a musical performance in the 1700s?",
    "choice1": "Saxophone",
    "choice2": "Harpsichord",
    "choice3": "Flute",
    "choice4": "Trumpet",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "Dances such as the Waltz, Bolero, and Minuet are usually written in what time signature?",
    "choice1": "4/4",
    "choice2": "6/8",
    "choice3": "12/8",
    "choice4": "3/4",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these tempo markings is the fastest?",
    "choice1": "Andante",
    "choice2": "Presto",
    "choice3": "Moderato",
    "choice4": "Allegro",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "Dynamic markings such as ff, f, mf, p, pp, represent words in what language?",
    "choice1": "Italian",
    "choice2": "French",
    "choice3": "German",
    "choice4": "English",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "What instruments comprise a standard string quartet?",
    "choice1": "Violin, Viola, Cello, Double Bass",
    "choice2": "4 Violins",
    "choice3": "2 Violins, Viola, Cello",
    "choice4": "Violin, Viola, Cello, Piano",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a reed instrument?",
    "choice1": "Oboe",
    "choice2": "Bassoon",
    "choice3": "Clarinet",
    "choice4": "Flute",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of the following terms refers to dynamics?",
    "choice1": "mezzoforte",
    "choice2": "adagio",
    "choice3": "coda",
    "choice4": "ritardando",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "To what year did Tchaikovsky dedicate a famous overture?",
    "choice1": "1912",
    "choice2": "1812",
    "choice3": "1712",
    "choice4": "1612",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "Adagio refers to what kind of pace within a piece of music?",
    "choice1": "Quiet",
    "choice2": "Fast",
    "choice3": "Slow",
    "choice4": "Loud",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "How many players are involved in a string quintet?",
    "choice1": "4",
    "choice2": "3",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "6",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "Who wrote the work 'The Four Seasons'?",
    "choice1": "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart",
    "choice2": "Johann Sebastian Bach",
    "choice3": "Ludwig van Beethoven",
    "choice4": "Antonio Vivaldi",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which family of instruments are NOT in a Concert Band?",
    "choice1": "Strings",
    "choice2": "Brass",
    "choice3": "Woodwind",
    "choice4": "Percussion",
    "answer": "1" }]